We've been waiting all morning.
Who are these people coming?
Seems like they're Manager Wen's enemies.
What are you talking about?
Is the live stream camera ready?
I'll get it ready right away.
Wen, are you still waiting?
Manager, you're here too.
It should be here.
Shouldn't I just make a phone call?
No.
I reported this matter.
I should resolve it myself.
All right.
Then I will have a good talk with them.
Let's go.
Sorry to trouble you this time, Manager.
It's what I should do.
They're here.
Start the livestream.
My big star.
You're finally here.
I have deleted the videos and articles on all accounts
and published a correction notice.
The details are written here.
Apologizing online
and deleting a video to solve this?
You're oversimplifying the problem.
Then what else do you want?
Who are you?
What does it have to do with you?
I think he looks familiar.
Anyway,
I want you to delete your accounts,
quit this industry,
and pay 2 million for the company's reputation damage.
The fake news did cause reputational damage to the company,
but you should be the one paying the compensation.
Me?
This fake news
cites a lot of internal confidential company information.
I've checked, and externally,
this part was only given to you.
I remember now.
You are the general manager of An'ers Group,
An Yufan.
Check it yourselves.
Mr. An,
please be the bigger person and forgive us.
It was our mistake this time.
As a PR company,
you actually took the initiative to leak company secrets
and create topics for public opinion.
Are you trying to target An'ers Group?
No, Mr. An.
Our boss is on his way back.
This was just an accident.
Please give us another chance.
You calculated the compensation quite well just now.
I'd like to hear
how the compensation for breach of contract should be calculated.
Mr. An, this is all a misunderstanding.
We will definitely provide a solution you're satisfied with.
Could we move to the meeting room?
This way, please.
Wen Lingli,
so many years have passed.
Why are you still targeting me?
You forgot everything.
Of course it's all in the past for you.
Lingli.
Brother Liang Chen,
you're here.
Are you going back?
Yes.
I really didn't expect
that Wang Yu would do something like student loans.
I was really out of my mind to believe him.
Lingli,
you should really control your temper.
Don't be so willful in the future.
Yeah.
Got it, Brother Chen.
Also,
I'm leaving too.
Immigrating to Canada with my mom.
Actually, we've had this plan for a while,
but there just wasn't the right opportunity.
After everything that's happened,
I've figured it out.
I won't run away anymore.
Then,
after you go abroad,
will you come back?
I don't know yet.
But it doesn't matter anymore.
I'm leaving.
Who says it doesn't matter?
It seems that this time,
you still won.
It really is you.
You looked familiar just now.
Don't you remember me?
Hi, Zixi.
Long time no see.
Do you still remember this?
Why do you have this?
It seems I guessed right.
You were the one
who hid it, right?
I...
Did you just see Yang Qian?
Yes.
But that doesn't matter anymore.
What matters is
that we are reunited.
Come with me somewhere.
Why are you back at school?
No one uses this anymore.
When I came back to school,
you had already forgotten me.
I often stayed here alone,
recalling everything we had been through.
I remembered how we met.
I remembered how we got to know each other.
And I remembered what I always wanted to say to you.
I wonder if you still remember this secret code.
Uncle He.
Uncle He is really something.
He knew all along but didn't tell me.
He probably planned to tell you at the right time.
The boss said to give this to you.
He said the room is only cleaned occasionally
and has been kept exactly as it was.
The room hasn't changed.
Wait a minute.
Okay.
I've been waiting for you for a long time.
Happy birthday.
Where did this diary come from?
It's probably magic.
Miss.
Over here.
Wow, your books are so new.
Yeah.
My daughter graduated from college and probably doesn't want to read them anymore.
Oh wow.
That's a diary, right?
Yes.
Oh.
Assistant Casting Director Xi Chongjing
Props Assistant Li Kunxiao
Production Vehicle Yi Mingle
Yitong